but eventually everybody comes to an accommodation except the palestinians the palestinian people
should know your leaders and the useful idiots on college campuses who are their allies are
not doing any favors by keeping alive the river to the sea myth i mean where do you think israel
is going spoiler alert nowhere he's such an ignorant sack of he hasn't a clue what the
history is he really doesn't know anything so what are the facts if you disagree with me have
me on your program already in 1976 the palestine liberation organization which at that point was
a representative organization the palestinian people were supporting two states on the june
1967 border they were supporting the compromise they were already giving up they gave up and i
hope this will sink into the minds of your listeners it's impossible that they'll sink into the mind of
bill mar because there isn't a mind there's a blank space that's filled in with desperate
attempts of being clever and funny for his paid listeners